logodesignteam.com 2019-01-19

# Privacy Policy - Logo Design by Logo Design Team - Custom Logo Design and Graphic Design Services

Effective from May 25, 2018

Key Definitions   
REGULATION (EU) 2016/679 OF THE EUROPEAN PARLIAMENT AND OF THE COUNCIL of 27 April 2016 on the protection of NATURAL PERSONS with regard to the processing of PERSONAL DATA and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation). 

1\. Consent:  
CONSENT means a clear affirmative act establishing a freely given, specific, informed and unambiguous indication of the website user’s agreement to the processing of personal data relating to him or her, such as by a written statement, including by electronic means, or an oral statement. 

2\. General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)  
Predominant objective of this protection is as follows: 

  * The processing of personal data should be designed to serve mankind.
  * Natural persons should have control of their own personal data;
  * The right to the protection of personal data is not an absolute right; it must be considered in relation to its function in society and be balanced against other fundamental rights, in accordance with the principle of proportionality.

3\. Personal Data  
Personal data means any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person (‘data subject’); an identifiable natural person is one who can be identified, directly or indirectly, in particular by reference to an identifier such as a name, an identification number, location data, an online identifier or to one or more factors specific to the physical, physiological, genetic, mental, economic, cultural or social identity of that natural person. 

4\. Websites  
It shall mean all websites as it may exist from time to time of Logo Design Team including but not limited to www.logodesignteam.com. 

GDPR specific rights can be enforced only for PERSONAL DATA collected of NATURAL PERSONS* (not a company, partnership or any other kind of Legal Entity). 

This privacy statement describes how A1 Future Technologies Pvt. Ltd. dba Logo Design Team ("Logo Design Team") collects and uses the personal information you provide on our Web site: www.logodesignteam.com. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information. 

Logo Design Team is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program. TRUSTe is an independent organization whose mission is to build user's trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. This privacy statement covers the Web site www.logodesignteam.com. Because this Web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe. 

This Policy is applicable to whosoever visits any of A1 Future Technologies Pvt. Ltd.. Logo Design Team and any service of A1Future Technologies Pvt. Ltd. being a partner, affiliate partner, reseller, and end customer. 

This Policy shall be legally binding on you and A1 Future Technologies Pvt. Ltd., on different activities on all our websites including but not limited to browsing through our websites, placing order on our websites, asking for quotation on website, reading blogs on our website, requesting a call back using our website or whatsoever purposes as a click-wrap contract between you and A1 Future Technologies Pvt. Ltd. 

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact Logo Design Team at dp@a1future.com. If you do not receive acknowledgement of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should contact TRUSTe at <https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request>   
TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with us to resolve your concerns. 

Collection and Use of Personal Information  
We collect the following personal information from you  
\- Contact Information such as name, email address, mailing address, phone number

We also collect the following information from you  
\- Information about your business such as company name, company size, business type 

As is true of most Web sites, we automatically gather information about your computer such as your IP address, browser type, referring/exit pages, and operating system using authority and reliable third-party tools. 

We do not knowingly collect any Personal Data from children under the age of 16. If you are under the age of 16, please do not submit any Personal Data through our Websites or Service(s). If you have reason to believe that a child under the age of 16 has provided Personal Data to us through our Websites or Service(s), please contact us and we will delete such personal information and terminate the child’s account from our databases. 

We use the information we collect from you to:

  * Fulfill your order
  * Send you an order confirmation
  * Assess the needs of your business to determine suitable products
  * Send you requested product or service information
  * Send product updates or warranty information
  * Respond to customer service requests
  * Administer your account
  * Register Resellers and answer Reseller Enquiries
  * Respond to your questions and concerns
  * Improve our Web site and marketing efforts
  * Conduct research and analysis

We use live chat to assist you with order processing. If our live chat is offline we will collect your name and email address so that we may reply to your request. 

Customer Testimonials  
We post customer testimonials on our Web site which may contain personally identifiable information. We do obtain the customer's consent via email prior to posting the testimonial to post their name and/or images along with their testimonial. 

Choice/Opt-Out  
We may periodically send promotional emails about new services, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided. 

From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests. 

We also send you product information that you have requested and other transactional emails related to your account and/or order. Generally, you may not opt-out of these transactional emails but for promotional emails you can choose to opt-out. 

RIGHT TO ACCESS, RECTIFY and/or DELETE PERSONAL DATA  
If you are a Reseller, Affiliate partner, Partner, Customer or an interested party, providing your personal data to A1 Future technologies Pvt. Ltd through any of its Website, applications or social media connects, blogs, corporate events, etc.; such data being collected for specific purposes mentioned hereunder Privacy Policy; you have the right to have access to your personal data provided to A1 Future Technologies Pvt. Ltd; and further you have the right to contact dp@a1future.com for rectification or deletion of your personal data, subject to other clauses of this policy; without affecting continuity of A1 Future Technologies Pvt. Ltd. ‘s business. Thus, deleting the User does not delete business-specific organization-owned data created and contributed to; by the User including without limitation, knowledgebase articles, notes, forum topics/comments, support calls, surveys, canned responses, ticket templates, order forms, order history, contacts, companies, tags, conversations in the tickets, email communications, comments or details provided on any third-party platform such as social media etc. 

Notwithstanding the foregoing, we will retain Service Data that may include your personal data as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, for litigation/defence purposes, maintain accurate financial and other records, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. 

Information Sharing  
We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement. We do not sell your personal information to third parties. We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as credit card processors or offering customer service. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us. 

We may also disclose your personal information 

  * As required by law such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process
  * When we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request,
  * Logo Design Team is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information,
  * to any other third party with your prior consent to do so.

Third Party E-Commerce Solutions Provider  
Our shopping cart is hosted by our e-commerce solutions providers. They host our ordering system, and collect your billing information directly from you for the purpose of processing your order. This company does not use this information for any other purpose. If you choose to use PayPal to finalize and pay for your order, you will provide your billing information, such as a credit card number, directly to PayPal. We will not have access to this information. PayPal's privacy policy will apply to the information you provide on the PayPal website. 

Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies  
We may use cookies, for example, to keep track of your preferences and profile information. Cookies are also used to collect general usage and volume statistical information that does not include personal information. 

Cookies set by the A1 Future are called “first party cookies”. Cookies set by parties other than the website owner are called “ third party cookies ” . Some cookies are required for technical reasons in order for our Websites and Services to function correctly, we refer to these as “ essential ” or “ strictly necessary ” cookies. Other cookies enable us and the third parties we work with to track and target the interests of visitors to our Websites, and we refer to these as “ Preferences ” or “ Statistics & Analytics” or “Marketing” cookies.   
The details of the cookies we use can be found in our Cookie Statement. 

Web beacons  
Our Web pages contain electronic images known as Web beacons (sometimes called single-pixel gifs) and are used along with cookies to compile aggregated statistics to analyze how our site is used and may be used in some of our emails to let us know which emails and links have been opened by recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of our customer communications and marketing campaigns. 

Third Party Tracking  
The use of cookies by our tracking utility company or service providers is not covered by our privacy statement. We do/do not have access or control over these tracking technologies cookies. You can read more about them in our Cookie Statement. 

Links to Other Web Sites  
Our Site includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of Logo Design Team. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy statements. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy statement of any Web site you visit. 

Security  
When we collect personal information directly from you, we follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at dp@a1future.com. 

In order to make a purchase from us, you must use our shopping cart provider to finalize and pay for your order. Its privacy statement and security practices will also apply to your information. We encourage you to read that privacy statement before providing your information. 

Additional Policy Information  
Correcting and Updating Your Personal Information  
To review and update your personal information to ensure it is accurate, contact us at [dp@a1future.com](mailto:dp@a1future.com). 

Notification of Privacy Statement Changes  
We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices.If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices. 

Whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that says “I Accept Privacy Policy & Cookie Policy ” . If you want to customize your cookie preference, you may contact us at [dp@a1future.com](mailto:dp@a1future.com) or follow the steps given in our Cookie Statement. 

If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at [dp@a1future.com](mailto:dp@a1future.com). 

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen. 

Alternatively, you can contact us by writing to us at the address below:  
A1 Future Technologies Pvt. Ltd.  
Dba Logo Design Team  
31 Raja Manindra Road  
Paik Para  
Kolkata, West Bengal 700037  
India  
Email: [dp@a1future.com](mailto:dp@a1future.com)
